<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
<title type="text">Dance Pirates</title>
<subtitle type="text">Get More Booty</subtitle>
<generator uri="https://github.com/mojombo/jekyll">Jekyll</generator>
<link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="/feed.xml" />
<link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="" />
<updated>2014-01-07T15:15:37-08:00</updated>
<id>/</id>
<author>
  <name>Captain Jack</name>
  <uri>/</uri>
  <email>jack@dancepirates.com</email>
</author>


<entry>
  <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Close Embrace Staircase]]></title>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="/exercises/the-close-embrace-staircase" />
  <id>/exercises/the-close-embrace-staircase</id>
  <published>2013-12-28T00:00:00-08:00</published>
  <updated>2013-12-28T00:00:00-08:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Captain Jack</name>
    <uri></uri>
    <email>jack@dancepirates.com</email>
  </author>
  <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Emphasize sensitivity, receptivity and consent throughout.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;prerequisites&quot;&gt;Prerequisites&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This works best with students who are already comfortable with the [90-10 rule] and dancing comfortably in close embrace.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;exercise&quot;&gt;Exercise&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Start with an introduction to the concept of the close embrace staircase:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;We can dance close embrace in many different ways.  Sometimes, you’re dancing with somebody you know well and you’re both melting into each other and dancing very intimately.  Sometimes, you’re dancing with somebody you don’t know as well and your close embrace is much more formal.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;We can think of close embrace connection as a staircase.  The bottom of the staircase is the most intimate/close/melty close embrace you can think of.  The top of the staircase is the most formal, impersonal close embrace you can think of.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Every single close embrace connection should start at the top of the staircase.  As you start dancing together, you can only move at most one step below your partner.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Demonstrate levels 1-10 with your partner, calling out each one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have students practice displaying and feeling the levels (but only down to level 6 or so, so avoid uncomfortability).&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/exercises/the-close-embrace-staircase&quot;&gt;The Close Embrace Staircase&lt;/a&gt; was originally published by Captain Jack at &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;Dance Pirates&lt;/a&gt; on December 28, 2013.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
</entry>


<entry>
  <title type="html"><![CDATA[Find Your Connection Muscles]]></title>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="/exercises/find-your-connection-muscles" />
  <id>/exercises/find-your-connection-muscles</id>
  <published>2013-12-28T00:00:00-08:00</published>
  <updated>2013-12-28T00:00:00-08:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Captain Jack</name>
    <uri></uri>
    <email>jack@dancepirates.com</email>
  </author>
  <content type="html">&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Repeat this exercise with both arms every day until you find your arms relaxing more as you dance.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Focus your thoughts on how the muscles feel when doing the exercise, both which ones are toned and which ones are relaxed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;exercise&quot;&gt;Exercise&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Find yourself a doorway.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Roll your right shoulder solidly into its socket, drawing your right shoulder blade down your spine and engaging your lats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Raise your right arm and stand close enough to the door that you can wrap your fingertips around the edge of the doorway with your elbow slightly bent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Settle your hips back so that you are lightly hanging onto the doorway to stay standing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Focus on your fingertips and your back, this is where most of the tone to hold you up should be. Try and relax the muscles in your arm as much as possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hold this position for at least 30 seconds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Repeat on the left side.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;tips&quot;&gt;Tips&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Be sure to maintain otherwise good posture while doing this. Keep your shoulders over your hips, your chest expanded and your head up.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/exercises/find-your-connection-muscles&quot;&gt;Find Your Connection Muscles&lt;/a&gt; was originally published by Captain Jack at &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;Dance Pirates&lt;/a&gt; on December 28, 2013.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
</entry>


<entry>
  <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 90-10 Rule of Close Embrace]]></title>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="/exercises/the-90-10-rule" />
  <id>/exercises/the-90-10-rule</id>
  <published>2013-12-26T00:00:00-08:00</published>
  <updated>2013-12-26T00:00:00-08:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Captain Jack</name>
    <uri></uri>
    <email>jack@dancepirates.com</email>
  </author>
  <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Emphasize consent throughout.  Close embrace is a touchy subject (no pun intended), so encourage students to focus on being receptive and respectful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;exercise&quot;&gt;Exercise&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Remember in that movie Hitch with Will Smith?  He plays a guy who teaches other guys how to be more confident with women.  He has one lesson in particular that’s well suited to getting into close embrace: the 90-10 rule.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hitch presents it in the context of kissing at the end of a first date.  Whoever is initiating the kiss can only go 90% of the way.  You can’t actually kiss them.  You ask a question by going that 90%, and they have to answer with the remaining 10%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We can think about close embrace the same way.  When you’re dancing with somebody, and you want to go into close embrace, you should only go 90% of the way to close embrace.  Don’t just pull them in.  If they want to go into close embrace, they’ll answer with the remaining 10%.  If they don’t answer or move back a little bit, go back to closed or whatever you were doing before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have students practice this idea.  Let both leads and follows practice asking for close embrace, and practice saying both ‘yes’ and ‘no’ and feeling the difference between the two responses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Discuss consent.  Talk about the reasons somebody might not want to dance in close embrace (self conscious, injury, don’t want to get you sweaty, uncomfortable) and encourage students to not take it personally.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Just because somebody has said ‘yes’ to close embrace with somebody else, doesn’t mean you should expect them to say ‘yes’ to you.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Just because somebody has said ‘yes’ to you before in the past, doesn’t mean you should expect them to say ‘yes’ to you.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Just because they’re currently saying ‘yes’ doesn’t mean you should expect them not to change their mind.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/exercises/the-90-10-rule&quot;&gt;The 90-10 Rule of Close Embrace&lt;/a&gt; was originally published by Captain Jack at &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;Dance Pirates&lt;/a&gt; on December 26, 2013.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
</entry>


<entry>
  <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Importance of Setting High Expecations]]></title>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="/pedagogy/setting-high-expectations" />
  <id>/pedagogy/setting-high-expectations</id>
  <updated>2013-12-26T00:00:00-00:00</updated>
  <published>2013-12-26T00:00:00-08:00</published>
  
  <author>
    <name>Captain Jack</name>
    <uri></uri>
    <email>jack@dancepirates.com</email>
  </author>
  <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;As instructors, we want our students to accomplish as much as possible in our classes.  One tactic some instructors employ to acheive this outcome is to set very high expectations for students.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The exact level of the expectation can vary somewhat from “probably acheivable” to “absolutely impossible”.  It’s also always a bit of a guessing game, since you never actually know quite what students are capable of.  But often, you’ll be surprised at how high your students will rise to meet your expectations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;make-expectations-psychological-not-physiological&quot;&gt;Make expectations psychological, not physiological&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;High expectations are particularly effective (especially at first) in driving student success when the blockers are mostly psychological, not physiological.  That is, when the problems are not about movement precision or artistic interpretation, but that there is some kind of mental block or lack of discipline that is holding students back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The problem with setting high expectations is that students can become frustrated and give up if they aren’t (or think they can’t) meet your expecations.  This is why I tend to set psychological instead of physiological expectations—it’s generally easier for students to change their behavior, but hard to master a new topic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, don’t set expectations for how quickly students progress, but do set expectations on how hard and how much students practice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;I expect you to practice these exercises at home for at least an hour before the next class.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;use-expectations-to-establish-an-effective-teacherstudent-relationship&quot;&gt;Use expectations to establish an effective teacher/student relationship&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take a moment (or several) at the beginning of class to set my expectations for student behavior.  Teaching and learning is a professional working relationship, so tell your students what actions and behaviors you need from them to make that relationship as effective as possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Avoid the perception of talking down to your students when setting these expectations.  Feeling like they are being treated like children lowers their perception of the expectations you’re setting for them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;When I say rotate, leads will thank their parters, rotate one partner counterclockwise, and introduce themselves to their new partners.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;After we rotate and make introductions, I know you’ll want to chat, but I need your voices off and your eyes up here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/pedagogy/setting-high-expectations&quot;&gt;The Importance of Setting High Expecations&lt;/a&gt; was originally published by Captain Jack at &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;Dance Pirates&lt;/a&gt; on December 26, 2013.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
</entry>


<entry>
  <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Ask Somebody To Dance]]></title>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="/exercises/how-to-ask-somebody-to-dance" />
  <id>/exercises/how-to-ask-somebody-to-dance</id>
  <published>2013-12-26T00:00:00-08:00</published>
  <updated>2013-12-26T00:00:00-08:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Captain Jack</name>
    <uri></uri>
    <email>jack@dancepirates.com</email>
  </author>
  <content type="html">&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Emphasize respect and consent throughout this exercise, especially around getting rejected for a dance.  Remind students that there are myriad reasons why the person they asked might not have wanted to dance, that they shouldn’t take it personally, and that &lt;em&gt;nobody&lt;/em&gt; owes anybody a dance.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;You may need to modify the exercise slightly depending on your local scene’s ettiquette about dancing with person B after you’ve rejected person A.  In some scenes it’s totally fine, in others it’s extremely rude.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Do all practice in both directions (i.e. side A ask side B, then side B ask side A).  Start with the bigger half asking the smaller half so people don’t feel immediately left out.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;exercise&quot;&gt;Exercise&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Split students in half.  Get half on one side of the room and half on the other.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Before we do anything else, we’re going to learn how to ask somebody to dance.  It’s harder than it seems, so pay attention.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-three-rules-of-asking-somebody-to-dance&quot;&gt;The Three Rules of Asking Somebody to Dance&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Introduce the Three Rules of asking somebody to dance.  Demonstrate a slight exaggeration of failing each rule with your partner, then briefly discuss why the rule exists.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;0. Smile!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s most effective to tie this one in with other discussions in the lesson about dancing primarily being about having fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;If you’re having fun and smiling, your partner is more likely to be excited about dancing with you and more likely to have a great time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1. Make eye contact&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Demo by coming up behind and asking over the shoulder.  It’s uncomfortable and students will immediately see that it’s uncomfortable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Generally, if you can’t establish good eye contact with somebody before you ask them to dance, you probably shouldn’t ask them this time.  This could be because they’re busy with something (e.g. a conversation), distracted or deep in thought, or just don’t want to dance this song.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2. Extend your hand (foot, head, etc)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Demo by asking to dance while standing a little too far away with hands clasped behind back (or in pockets).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You should give the person you’re asking to dance an invitation to initiate a physical connection.  This one is a little flexible, since dancing with somebody doesn’t necessarily need to involve touching them, but it’s still best practice to ask with an open and inviting posture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3. Verbalize the request–actually ask them to dance!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Demo by dramatically thrusting a hand out and giving a deep smouldering look.  Students will laugh.  Emphasize that some people actually do this because they think they look cool, but this is how they actually look.  Optionally, demo the grab-n-drag to bring up consent more explicitly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the most important rule.  Not only is asking out loud polite, but it gives the person you’ve asked a chance to say no.  Yay, consent!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;practice&quot;&gt;Practice&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[Call and response] the rules once or twice to cement them in the students’ minds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Half the students ask the other half, and the askee will say ‘Yes!’.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Explain that now students are going to practice saying ‘no’ and being rejected.  Encourage students to give excuses if they’re true (about to go get water, bathroom, sitting out), but emphasize that they don’t need an excuse–a simple “No, thank you.” is fine–and to not lie about an excuse.  Discuss your scene’s ettiquette around saying ‘yes’ to person B after you’ve rejected person A.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Discuss the reasons somebody might say no: injury, not liking the song, not being in the mood, etc.  Encourage students to not take it personally if they get rejected for a dance, but just to brush it off and ask somebody else.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Half the students ask the other half.  The askee will say ‘No, thank you’ (or some variation) to the first ask and ‘yes’ to the second ask.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before the second half of this last time practicing (i.e. when half B asks half A), you can tell students to bring the partner who says ‘yes’ to a spot in a circle around you and proceed with your lesson.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[Call and response] the rules one more time during the lesson, either after the last time practicing or at the end.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/exercises/how-to-ask-somebody-to-dance&quot;&gt;How to Ask Somebody To Dance&lt;/a&gt; was originally published by Captain Jack at &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;Dance Pirates&lt;/a&gt; on December 26, 2013.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
</entry>


<entry>
  <title type="html"><![CDATA[Call and Response]]></title>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="/pedagogy/call-and-response" />
  <id>/pedagogy/call-and-response</id>
  <updated>2013-12-21T00:00:00-00:00</updated>
  <published>2013-12-26T00:00:00-08:00</published>
  
  <author>
    <name>Captain Jack</name>
    <uri></uri>
    <email>jack@dancepirates.com</email>
  </author>
  <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;It’s useful to be able to confirm that students have actually learned something, and to encourage memorization of certain concepts.  To do this, you can employ call and response.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To make this work, you need to deeply and closely associate a call phrase and a response phrase.  There are a couple ways to do this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Very explicitly tell students what the call and response are.  Effective, but a little heavy-handed and connects the ideas in a very shallow way.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;When I say …, you say …&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Say the call and response together a few times.  Use as close to the same phrasing each time as you can, and say it with a very slightly singsongy tone.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Rule 0 is to always smile.  When you smile at your partner, they like you more and have more fun.  So, don’t forget, rule 0 is to smile.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Immediately after establishing the call and response, use it.  Say/ask the call phrase, then lean forward a bit and make a ‘your turn’ gesture to the students.  Encourage the students who respond.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;What’s rule 0?  [Always smile!]  Good!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Use the call and response a few times over the course of the lesson, and once right at the end to cement it.  If you’re doing a series, bring it back in later weeks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;examples&quot;&gt;Examples&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before class auditions at Blues Muse, Carsie and the gang used a call and response to get participants engaged and relaxed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;What are we doing?  Dancing!  Why are we doing it?  Just for fun!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She used the explicit form since it was such large group and it was getting students to say aloud and reinforce something they already knew.  It worked fantastically well, and students were much less nervous going into auditions.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/pedagogy/call-and-response&quot;&gt;Call and Response&lt;/a&gt; was originally published by Captain Jack at &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;Dance Pirates&lt;/a&gt; on December 26, 2013.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
</entry>


<entry>
  <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spinning Practice]]></title>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="/exercises/spinning-practice" />
  <id>/exercises/spinning-practice</id>
  <published>2013-12-22T00:00:00-08:00</published>
  <updated>2013-12-22T00:00:00-08:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Captain Jack</name>
    <uri></uri>
    <email>jack@dancepirates.com</email>
  </author>
  <content type="html">&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Each exercise should be done on both feet and in both directions, where applicable.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Turning is a skill, not a talent.  Spend 5 minutes a day practicing these and you will get better.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Throughout, keep an emphasis on precision, not power or speed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;exercise&quot;&gt;Exercise&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Start with balancing on one foot for 30s - 1m.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Repeat on relevé (balancing on the ball of the foot).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From a small plie, launch onto relevé and hold balance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From a small plie, launch into a quarter turn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;… half turn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;… full turn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;… double turn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;… triple turn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Keep going until your students are in awe of your turning ability.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;tips&quot;&gt;Tips&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Engaging your [[core]] helps you maintain your [[axis]], which helps you maintain your balance.  Maintain [[good posture]].&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;For best practice, attempt to end each turn on balance.  That is, the turn should end–you should stop moving–while you’re still in relevé.  Then after a moment’s pause, relax.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/exercises/spinning-practice&quot;&gt;Spinning Practice&lt;/a&gt; was originally published by Captain Jack at &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;Dance Pirates&lt;/a&gt; on December 22, 2013.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
</entry>


<entry>
  <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show and Go]]></title>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="/pedagogy/show-and-go" />
  <id>/pedagogy/show-and-go</id>
  <updated>2013-12-21T00:00:00-00:00</updated>
  <published>2013-12-22T00:00:00-08:00</published>
  
  <author>
    <name>Captain Jack</name>
    <uri></uri>
    <email>jack@dancepirates.com</email>
  </author>
  <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Begin by setting an expectation for what’s about to happen&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;We’re going to demo this move 5 times.  At the end of those 5 times, you’re going to do it.  Watch carefully.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Demo the move, changing orientations/directions and counting each time.  Most importantly, SHUT UP while demoing.  Let the students concentrate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the end of the 5 times, let them try it twice.  They’re going to fail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rotate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;You all want to see it again?  Ok, we’re going to show the move 3 more times.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Demo 3 or 4 more times.  You should get some great ‘OHHHH’ sounds.  Very satisfying.  Let them try it again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rotate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Walk students through the move.  Point things out through questions:  “Which foot am I spinning on?”  “Where does my hand go?”  If students have questions of their own, tease the question out into something they can observe, then demo the move.  Let them try it more times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rotate.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/pedagogy/show-and-go&quot;&gt;Show and Go&lt;/a&gt; was originally published by Captain Jack at &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;Dance Pirates&lt;/a&gt; on December 22, 2013.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
</entry>

</feed>